http://www.imanami.com/privacy-policy/

Skip to contentGroupIDSolutions OverviewAutomateSelf ServiceSynchronizePassword CenterReportsAuthenticatePhoneIDHealth MeterInsightsResourcesResource CenterBlogDocumentation LibrarySupportSubmit a requestKnowledge BaseCommunity LinksSupport
LifecycleSupport OptionsAboutCorporate BackgroundCareersPartnersContactFree TrialPrivacy PolicyIf you do not agree to these terms, please do not access or use this site. Imanami reserves the right to change the Online Privacy Policy from time to time at its sole discretion. Your use of this site will be subject to the most current version of the Online Privacy Policy at the time of such use.Collection of Personal InformationWhen you engage in certain activities on this site, such as ordering or registering products, downloading software, or entering contests, Imanami may ask you to provide certain information about yourself by filling out and submitting an online form. It is completely optional for you to engage in these activities. If you elect to engage in these activities, however, Imanami may ask that you provide us personal information, such as your first and last name, mailing address (including zip code), e-mail address, employer, job title and department, telephone and facsimile numbers, and other personal identifying information. When ordering products or services on the site, you may be asked to provide a credit card number. Depending upon the activity, some of the information that we ask you to provide is identified as mandatory and some as voluntary. If you do not provide the mandatory data with respect to a particular activity, you will not be able to engage in that activity.When you submit personal information to Imanami on this site, you understand and agree that this information may be transferred across national boundaries and may be stored and processed in any of the countries in which Imanami and its affiliates and subsidiaries maintain offices, including without limitation, the United States. You also acknowledge that in certain countries or with respect to certain activities, the collection, transferring, storage and processing of your information may be undertaken by trusted vendors of Imanami.How your Personal Information is UsedImanami collects your information in order to record and support your participation in the activities you select. If you order a product that is to be electronically downloaded, for example, the information is used to register your license and rights, if any, to technical support, upgrade discounts, or other benefits that may be made available to registered users. If you enter a contest, information is collected to qualify the entry and contact you regarding the contest or prize awards. The information that you provide is also used as part of our effort to keep you informed about product upgrades, special offers, and other products and services of Imanami and selected third parties.Your Choices with Respect to Personal InformationImanami recognizes and appreciates the importance of responsible use of information collected on this site. If you do not want the information you provide to Imanami to be used to inform you of other products, services and special offers available from Imanami, and you indicate this preference when you provide your personal information to Imanami, Imanami will honor your preference. In addition, Imanami may selectively provide certain information to other companies or organizations that have products or services we think may interest you. If you do not want to receive promotional materials regarding third party products or services, and you indicate this preference when you provide your personal information to Imanami, Imanami will honor your preference by not providing your information to such third parties. Imanami reserves the right to provide aggregate data to third parties for statistical analysis. Such data will not be linked to any particular individuals.Protection of your Personal InformationThe personal information that you provide in connection with registering yourself as an Imanami user or registering an Imanami product is classified as Registration Information. In addition, your Registration Information resides on a secure server that only selected Imanami personnel and contractors have access to via password. Imanami encrypts your personal information and thereby prevents unauthorized parties from viewing such information when it is transmitted to Imanami.Since this information is not accessible from outside Imanami, you will not be asked to select a password in order to view or modify such information.Please note that any information you post to a public bulletin board or chat room, such as the Imanami User to User Forums, is available to all persons accessing that site.Use of CookiesWhen you visit Imanami.com, you can surf the site anonymously and access important information without revealing your identity. In order to improve our site, we use “cookies” to track your visit. A cookie is small amount of data that is transferred to your browser by a Web server and can only be read by the server that gave it to you. It functions as your identification card, recording your passwords, purchases, and preferences. It cannot be executed as code or deliver viruses.Most browsers are initially set to accept cookies. You can set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether or not to accept it. (For some Web pages that require an authorization, cookies are not optional. Users choosing not to accept cookies will probably not be able to access those pages.)While Imanami uses cookies to track your visit to Imanami.com, and our Web servers automatically log the IP/Internet address of your computer, this information does not identify you personally and you remain anonymous unless you have otherwise provided Imanami with personal information.Privacy Related ComplaintsIf you believe that Imanami has not complied with this Online Privacy Policy with respect to your personal information, you may write the Imanami Privacy Officer. In your letter, please describe in as much detail as possible the ways in which you believe that the Imanami Online Privacy Policy has not been complied with. We will investigate your complaint promptly. Please note that if you provide Imanami with inconsistent privacy preferences (for example, by indicating on one occasion that third parties may contact you with marketing offers and indicating on another occasion that they may not), Imanami cannot guarantee that your most recent privacy preference will be honored. Also, please note that Imanami is not responsible for the content or privacy practices of non-Imanami Web sites to which Imanami.com or any other Imanami Web site may link.(925) 371-3000 Find us on:Facebook page opens in new windowTwitter page opens in new windowYouTube page opens in new windowLinkedin page opens in new window
Any Questions? GroupIDAutomateSelf ServiceSynchronizePassword CenterReportsAuthenticatePhoneIDHealth MeterInsightsWhy Imanami?Solutions OverviewIndustry WhitepapersForrester ReportSUPPORTSubmit a requestContact SupportSupport LifecycleSupport OptionsKnowledge
BaseCommunity Links
© 2020 Imanami Corporation.Terms & conditions, features, support, pricing and service options are subject to change without notice.
| Legal |
Privacy | Go to Top
Register a Deal[wpp_insert]×
